{
    "question": "Contoh dialog bahasa inggris tentang expressing threatening/threat ?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "A : Hey, when do you want to pay your debt?<br>B : I will do my best to pay it next week.<br>A : It&#039;s better for you to keep your words, otherwise Don Corleone will kill you\u00a0<br>B : DOn&#039;t worry sir, I will keep my words",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "terdiri-dari-apa-sajakah-causative-have-itu-798",
            "question": "Terdiri dari apa sajakah causative have itu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Causative verb menunjukkan bahwa seseorang/sesuatu secara tidak langsung bertanggung jawab terhadap sebuah tindakan. Subjek tidak melakukan tindakan itu sendiri, tetapi justru menyebabkan seseorang/sesuatu yang lain melakukannya. Contoh:<br>- Yesterday I had my hair cut.<br>Pembicara pada kalimat diatas tidak memotong sendiri rambutnya, tetapi justru membuat orang lain melakukannya \u2013 Saya \u201cmenyebabkan\u201d mereka memotong rambut saya.<br>Have<br>Have merupakan causative verb yang umum. Ketimbang melakukan sesuatu dengan diri kita sendiri, kita \u201cmenyuruh\u201d orang yang lain untuk melakukannya. Bentuknya sebagai berikut:<br>Kata kerja \u201cto have\u201d + objek + past participle (verb 3). Contoh:<br>- I had my jacket cleaned yesterday.<br>- Did you have your computer fixed?<br>Terkadang kita menggunakan have sebagai causative verb ketika kita ingin melakukan tindakan oleh diri kita sendiri. Contoh:<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll do it by tomorrow morning. &gt;&gt;<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll have it done by tomorrow morning.<br>Dengan menggunakan causative, kalimat ke-dua diatas mengalihkan perhatian dari pelaku tindakan, dan lebih memberikan perhatian kepada tindakan yang sedang dilakukan. Ini kedengaran sopan dan profesional.<br>Get<br>Get sering digunakan ketimbang have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI got my computer fixed \u2013 I had my computer fixed. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>\u2022\tI got my jacket cleaned. \u2013 I had my jacket cleaned. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>Causative verbs sering digunakan bersama dengan pengalaman-pengalaman negatif. Pada situasi-situasi ini lebih umum menggunakan have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI had my wallet stolen. (Saya sebenarnya tidak menyebabkan dompet saya dicuri \u2013 seseorang mencuri dompet saya dariku)<br><span>\u2022\tShe had her window smashed.<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantu-nyusun-kata-kata-ne-jadi-klimat-yg-bner-ya-yang-dimulai-dri-452",
            "question": "Bantu nyusun kata-kata ne jadi klimat yg bner ya yang dimulai dri yg bergaris bawah sama bantu buatkan CONDITIONAL SENTENCE TIPE 2    arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words.\r\n1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place\r\n2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\u00a0mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. If\u00a0 I know his phone number, I will invite Finto to the puppet show at my place.<br>2. If Mr. Kukuh and his family go to Bali, they will have a long holiday to Lombok this year.<br>Sorry kalau salah, baru pemula hehehe<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "choose-the-inappropriate-structure-in-the-following-sentences-rim-675",
            "question": "Choose the inappropriate structure in the following sentences    rima : they said the exam was complicated. Do You think so ?\r\nAmi : I Disagree with you. You can see that everyone's score is satisfied.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "rima : they\u00a0<u>said\u00a0</u><span>the exam complicated. Did\u00a0You\u00a0</span><u>think\u00a0</u>so ?<br><span>Ami : I\u00a0was\u00a0</span><u>Disagree</u><span>\u00a0with you. You can saw that everyone&#039;s score was\u00a0</span><u>satisfied.</u>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "rima : they\u00a0<u>said\u00a0</u>the exam complicated. Did\u00a0You\u00a0<u>think\u00a0</u>so ?<br>Ami : I\u00a0was\u00a0<u>Disagree</u>\u00a0with you. You can saw that everyone&#039;s score was\u00a0<u>satisfied.</u>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-yang-membuatmu-suka-dengan-cerita-malin-kundang-apa-saja-yg-d-727",
            "question": "Apa yang membuatmu suka dengan cerita malin kundang    apa saja yg dapat diambil (pelajaran) dari cerita tersebut?? (minimal 2)\r\n\r\njawabnya pakai bahasa inggris y.. \r\nplease....",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "tidak boleh membantah kedua orang tua ..<br>maaf gk bisa bhs. inggris !!<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. bercerita realiti dan fakta<br>2. bisa dijadikan pelajaran buat kita<br><br>hikmhanx kita tidak boleh melawan ortu terutama ibu kita,, karena dia yg mengandung kita selama 9 bulan",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-beri-penjelasan-tentang-word-order-dengan-rinci-844",
            "question": "Tolong Beri Penjelasan Tentang Word Order\u00a0Dengan Rinci",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Word order atau tata urut kata merupakan cara untuk\nmenyusun kata \u2013 kata dalam urutan atau susunan yang tepat dan benar. </span>\n\n<br><br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Word order adalah susunan kata-kata dalam kalimat, artinya bahwa cara kita menempatkan setiap kata itu haruslah sesuai dengan fungsinya dalam membentuk suatu kalimat. Caranya dengan mengetahui dan menghafal rumus atau pola baku.<br>Contoh:<br>&#039;&#039; Sebuah mobil mewah baru buatan Amerika Serikat &#039;&#039; diterjemahkan menjadi \" A new American car \".<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "minta-tolong-kasi-contoh-percakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pernya-886",
            "question": "Minta tolong kasi contoh percakapan bahasa inggris tentang pernyataan setuju dan tidak setuju",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Class Vacation<br><br><span>Yoga\t: So, class. Now we are going to deliberate our concern about where we are going to head for our class vacation. So, who comes up with the idea first?<br>Habibi\t: I will vote for Anyer Beach. Anyer Beach is one of the nearest beaches we can visit.<br>Yoga\t: So, class. Is there anyone who disagrees with Anyer Beach?<br>Jenny\t: Um, I am not sure about that. Last vacation our class had gone to Anyer Beach. I think we should see other options.<br>Habibi\t: Oh yeah! You\u2019re right, I forgot about that.<br>Jefri\t: Well, I\u2019m suggesting Kebun Raya Bogor<br>Kania\t: I agree with you, Jefri. I have never been there myself.<br>Geri\t: Me too, I am with you, Kania. Seeing great trees and plants must be exciting. Kebun Raya Bogor is like a great jungle in the middle of town.<br>Sarah\t: I\u2019m sorry guys. I think I will disagree with that. It\u2019s rainy season now. And as you know, Kebun Raya Bogor is located in Bogor which is the city of rain. And seeing the intensity of rainfall throughout Indonesia lately, I think we might not be able to explore the whole Kebun Raya Bogor due to the rain.<br>Tio\t: I think what Sarah said is right. Kebun Raya Bogor is not the best place to visit during this heavy rainy season<br>Yoga\t: Well, are there any other options?<br>Fauzi\t: How about Bali?<br>Habibi\t: No way! I don\u2019t have enough money to go to Bali<br>Sarah\t: Habibi is right, Fauzi. It\u2019s really costly to pick Bali as an option.<br>Yoga\t: Okay, class. To save the time, now let\u2019s just write your idea into a piece of paper and we will deliberate in the next occasion. Thank you.<br><br>contoh yang lebih simple lagi :)<br><br></span>A : hi, good morning B<br>B : morning A, how are you??<br>A : i&#039;m fine thank&#039;s<br>B : are you agree if i break up with C??<br>A : no, i don&#039;t<br>B : why??<br>A : I&#039;m not agree if you break up with C, because she more Love you then anyone, bro don&#039;t break up with her, and maybe sometime you can&#039;t find girl like C anymore, so don&#039;t break up with her<br>B : uhh, okay broooo, thank&#039;s for that<br><span>A : your welcome dude....<br></span><br>sekian dari saya :D",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Lin :I can&#039;t help to hold on any longer.<br>Sara : Oh why?<br>Lin : I think he truly never cares about me. He keeps talking about his ex-girl friend and it hurts me. He doesn&#039;t love me anymore!<br>Sara : <em>I don&#039;t think so</em>, Lin! Jey does love you so much. I know it. You&#039;re everything to him. Probably he did that just want to know how your response is. He wants to know whether you love him as he loves you. Ask him yourself and keep positive thinking. Don&#039;t ever let him go because of your emotion.<br>Lin : <em><strong>I think you&#039;re right</strong></em>. It might be better to talk to him directly. Thanks, Sara.<br>Sara : you are very welcome.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-certia-bahasa-inggris-last-vocation-892",
            "question": "Contoh certia bahasa inggris \"last vocation\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "It&#039;s curious as we grow older, how easy it is to lose our sense of \ndirection, a sense of vocation, a sense of God&#039;s calling us to important\n things still to be done. Vocations are not just for the young starting \nout in marriage, a career, or religious life. There&#039;s another kind of \nvocation \u2014 a kind of \"late vocation\" \u2014 God&#039;s final call to a strong \nfinish. It is God&#039;s call to each one of us to grow old gracefully \u2014 full\n of grace \u2014 to grow toward Him.    \nGod calls us to respond heroically, like Saint Paul, pouring ourselves \nout like a libation until we can say: \"I have fought the good fight, I \nhave finished the race, I have kept the faith\" (II Tm 7).<span><br><br><br>INI</span>\u00a0?\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ubah-kalimat-tersebut-ke-dalam-bentuk-pasif-1-it-is-said-that-ma-237",
            "question": "Ubah kalimat tersebut ke dalam bentuk pasif    1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods\r\n2. People say that Arthur is very rich\r\n3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods<br>-- ini udah pasif ya?\u00a0<br>Many people are homeless due to flood, it is said by the newspaper<br><br>2. People say that Arthur is very rich<br>Arthur is very rich, is said by people<br><span><br>3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0<br>he has 22 children, is said by people\u00a0<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-798",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Keindahan alam :<br>A: Wow! such a beautiful park.<br>B: Yea! i think so.<br><br>2. Teacher :<br>A: Thanks Miss jasmine! i understand it well than before.<br>B: Your welcome.<br><br>Semoga membantu :D",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Alam <br>A : Look at that beautiful lake !<br>B : Amazing<br>Mother<br>A : mom, you look pretty everytime !<br>B : thank you dear<br>Father\u00a0<br>A : Dad, you cook this ?<br>B : Yup.<br>A : waw, you can be a great chef<br>Grandpa<br>A: Grandpa, do you made this toys ?<br>B : yes, my dear<br>A : its look amazing !<br>Brother<br>A : Hey, you made this story ?<br>B: yup<br>A : Its so funny ! i love it<br>Teacher\u00a0<br>A : Sir, I never met a great teacher like you<br>B : thank you<br>friend :<br>A : Hey, you look pretty when you wear that dress<br>B : really ? thank you !<br>Best friend per<br>A : your cat is so cute.<br>B: Hahaha, yes, i know that<br>Yourself :<br>A : Hey, i look beautifull with this t-shirt !",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}